{
  "chapter": 8,
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "By which kind of hardware components makes cloud computing cost effective at the time of building resource pools?",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Commodity hardware",
        "Specialized hardware",
        "Both a and b",
        "None of these"
      ],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Resource pools are organized in",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Heap structure",
        "Hierarchical structure",
        "Hash structure",
        "None of these"
      ],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "The traditional approach of having discrete and independent set of resources is known as",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Warehouse",
        "Data center",
        "Silos",
        "None of these"
      ],
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Resource pools at cloud data centers are created with",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Specialized hardware components",
        "Commodity hardware components",
        "Costly hardware components",
        "None of these"
      ],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Multi-tenancy in cloud computing is powered by",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Ownership of free resource sharing",
        "Temporary resource allocation",
        "Resource allocation in virtual mode",
        "All of these"
      ],
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "In cloud computing, resource provisioning to consumers are made through",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Physical servers",
        "Virtual private network",
        "Virtual machines",
        "None of these"
      ],
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "In static provisioning of resources, resource allocation decision is taken",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Before starting of application",
        "Any time before and after starting of application",
        "Only once",
        "Both a and c"
      ],
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "In dynamic provisioning of resources, the resource allocation decision can be taken",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "After starting of application",
        "On-demand",
        "For number of times",
        "All of these"
      ],
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "Dynamic resource provisioning approach eliminates the problem(s) of",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Resource under-provisioning",
        "Resource over-provisioning",
        "Both a and b",
        "System speed"
      ],
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Zero downtime system architecture is outcome of",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Dynamic provisioning",
        "Multi-tenancy",
        "Resource sharing",
        "Resource pooling"
      ],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Standardization of cloud environment is done over the",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Physical resource pool",
        "Virtualized resource pool",
        "Individual physical resources",
        "None of these"
      ],
      "answer": 2
    }
  ]
}
